Ellen L. Lutz Papers MS177
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Publications, presentations and conference files, 1942 -- 2009; 1985 -- 2008; MS177.010; 10.8 Linear Feet; 5 Digital Object(s)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State] Table summaries and CD: Mali - Traore, 1991 -- 2003; MS177.010.019.00012 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State] Table summaries and CD: Nigeria, Abacha Sons: Obasanjo - Abubaker, 1995 -- 2005; MS177.010.019.00013 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State] Table summaries and CD: Rwanda: Jean Kambanda (arguably, Bizimungu), 2007; MS177.010.019.00014 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State] Table summaries and CD: Sierra Leone - (junta members), 2003 -- 2005; MS177.010.019.00015 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State] Table summaries and CD: Zambia - Chiluba (ongoing), 1997 -- 2007; MS177.010.019.00016 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State] Table summaries and CD: Zimbabwe - Banana, 1997 -- 2007; MS177.010.019.00017 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State] Table summaries and CD: Neatly indicted - Kenya, Uganda - Idi Amin, 2001 -- 2005; MS177.010.019.00018 (Box 19)
  - Corruption articles / treaties, 2006 -- 2007; MS177.010.019.00020 (Box 19)
  - Universal jurisdiction articles, 2007; MS177.010.019.00021 (Box 19)
  - Freedom House 2007 Rpt, MS177.010.019.00022 (Box 19)
  - Hybrid counts, 2006; MS177.010.019.00023 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Asia research files] Cambodia: Khmer Rouge, 2002 -- 2005; MS177.010.019.00024 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Asia research files] India: Former PM Roa, Cabinet Minister, Buta Singh, 1996 -- 2005; MS177.010.019.00025 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Asia research files] India - Rajiv Gandhi (PM), (charged and cleared posthumously of corruption charges), 1999 -- 2005; MS177.010.019.00026 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Asia research files] India - Laloo Prasao Yadav, Provincial Governor, then Railway Minister, 2004 -- 2005; MS177.010.019.00027 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Asia research files] Indonesia: Akbar Tanjung (Parliamentary Speaker, possible presidential candidate), 2002 -- 2005; MS177.010.019.00028 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Asia research files] Indonesia: Tommy Suharto, 1998 -- 2005; MS177.010.019.00029 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Asia research files] Indonesia: Suharto 'Sr.', 1998 -- 2001; MS177.010.019.00030 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Asia research files] Indonesia: Human rights court cases (East Timor), 2002 -- 2005; MS177.010.019.00031 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Asia research files] Japan - Kakuei Tanaka (PM 1972-1974), 1976 -- 2005; MS177.010.019.00032 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Asia research files] Kazakhstan: 'Kazakhgate,' Nursultan Nazarbayev and Nurlan Balgimbayev, 2001 -- 2005; MS177.010.019.00033 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Asia research files] Malaysia - Anwar Ibrahim, 1998 -- 2005; MS177.010.019.00034 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Asia research files] Nepal: Chiranjivi Wangle, former acting PM (Info and Broadcasting Minister), 1997 -- 2005; MS177.010.019.00035 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Asia research files] Pakistan: General info and Zulfikar Ali Bhutto, Benazir Bhutto's father, 1979 -- 2002; MS177.010.019.00036 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Asia research files] Pakistan: Nawaz Sharif, 1993 -- 2005; MS177.010.019.00037 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Asia research files] Pakistan: Benazir Bhutto, 1993 -- 2005; MS177.010.019.00038 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Asia research files] South Korea - Chun Doo Hwan (ex-president) and Roh Tae Woo (Hwan's successor), 1995 -- 2001; MS177.010.019.00039 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Asia research files] Thailand: Thaksin Shinawatra, 2000 -- 2005; MS177.010.019.00040 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Asia research files] Thailand: Rakkiat Sukthana, former Public Health Minister, 2003 -- 2005; MS177.010.019.00041 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Asia research files] Turkmenistan: Boris Shikhmuradov (former Foreign Minister), 2002 -- 2005; MS177.010.019.00042 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Asia research files] Philippines - Estrad, 2001 -- 2005; MS177.010.019.00043 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Human Rights and Conflilct Resolution in Context, chapter drafts and correspondence], 2004 -- 2005; MS177.010.019.00044 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Human Rights and Conflilct Resolution in Context, manuscript, 1 of 4], 2008; MS177.010.019.00045 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Human Rights and Conflilct Resolution in Context, manuscript, 2 of 4], 2008; MS177.010.019.00046 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Human Rights and Conflilct Resolution in Context, manuscript, 3 of 4], 2008; MS177.010.019.00047 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Human Rights and Conflilct Resolution in Context, manuscript, 4 of 4], 2008; MS177.010.019.00048 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Human Rights and Conflilct Resolution in Context, chapter drafts and correspondence], 2004 -- 2007; MS177.010.019.00049 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Human Rights and Conflilct Resolution in Context, chapter drafts and correspondence], 2005; MS177.010.019.00050 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Human Rights and Conflilct Resolution in Context, chapter drafts and correspondence], 2003 -- 2004; MS177.010.019.00051 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Human Rights and Conflilct Resolution in Context] Rockefeller book [notes and correspondence], 2003; MS177.010.019.00052 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Human Rights and Conflilct Resolution in Context] Rockefeller book [authors' conference], 2003; MS177.010.019.00053 (Box 19)
  - ['The Right to Reparations for Violations of Human Rights': drafts, lecture notes and research, 1 of 3], 1993 -- 1997; MS177.010.020.00015 (Box MS177 Shared 6)
    This file is related to material in Box 12, Folder 40 of the Publications, presentations and conference files series.
  - ['The Right to Reparations for Violations of Human Rights': drafts, lecture notes and research, 2 of 3], 1995; MS177.010.020.00016 (Box MS177 Shared 6)
  - ['The Right to Reparations for Violations of Human Rights': drafts, lecture notes and research, 3 of 3], 1995; MS177.010.020.00017 (Box MS177 Shared 6)
  - Brutality Unchecked: Human Rights Abuses Along the U.S. Border with Mexico, an Americas Watch Report, 1991; MS177.010.047.00022 (Box MS177 Shared 4)
  - Prosecuting Heads of State files from external hard drive, 2009; MS177.010.047.00042
  - HRCR Book, 2003-07-10; MS177.010.047.00043
  - IELPOLCA, WP 5.1, materials re political cases, 1998-02-05; MS177.010.047.00044
- General research materials, 1970 -- 2010; MS177.011; 7.2 Linear Feet
  This series contains literature collected by Lutz regarding topics in human rights and dating from approximately 1970 through 2010.
  This series is arranged as received, at the box level.
  - General research materials, 1970 -- 2010; MS177.011.003 (Box 3)
  - General research materials, 1970 -- 2010; MS177.011.004 (Box 4)
  - General research materials, 1970 -- 2010; MS177.011.005 (Box 5)
  - General research materials, 1970 -- 2010; MS177.011.006 (Box 6)
  - General research materials, 1970 -- 2010; MS177.011.007 (Box 7)
  - General research materials, 1976 -- 2006; MS177.011.043.00010 (Box MS177 Shared 3)
- Additional accessions, MS177.001822
  - Correspondence, MS177-001 (Box 1)
  - Mediation and arbitration electronic files, MS177-002
  - Marcos litigation electronic files, MS177-003
  - Digital files, MS177-004